{
  "type": "writing",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Qù" ,
      "answer": "去"
    },
    {
      "question": "Yóuyǒng",
      "answer": "游泳"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zuótiān" ,
      "answer": "昨天"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jīngjù",
      "answer": "京剧"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zěnme yàng",
      "answer": "怎么样"
    },
    {
      "question": "Yǒuyìsi",
      "answer": "有意思"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jīntiān",
      "answer": "今天"
    },
    {
      "question": "tiān",
      "answer": "天"
    },
    {
      "question": "Tiānqì",
      "answer": "天气"
    },
    {
      "question": "Tài",
      "answer": "太"
    },
    {
      "question": "Shénme",
      "answer": "什么"
    },
    {
      "question": "Shíhòu",
      "answer": "时候"
    },
    {
      "question": "Xiànzài",
      "answer": "现在"
    }
  ]
}
